# Ignacio González

London, United Kingdom www.nachogl1.dev i.gonzalezl@hotmail.com +44 7395454415

# **Profile**

~4 years experienced Full-Stack software developer with a MSc in Computer Science and BSc in Bilingual Biomedical Engineering. I bring good energy and a hard working mindset, I am easy to work with and try to provide value above what is expected. I have developed a few pet projects and created some content around programming, more info can be found in <a href="https://www.nachogl1.dev">www.nachogl1.dev</a>. Other interests are padel, brazilian jiu jitsu, productivity and finances.

# **Relevant Experience**

#### April 2022- Jul 2024

## Software Craftsperson, Codurance, London, UK

- Working in a technology agnostic software consultancy whose central core is composed of best practices and basics like SOLID principles, Agile and methodologies like XP using practices like pair programming. Codurances core values are Pragmatism, Excellence, Professionalism, Efficiency and Respect
  - Client 1: Search Engine. TS, AWS OpenSearch, AWS Lambdas and Cucumber. We worked on the ETL layer that receives data about bookings/accommodations, feeds them correctly into the search engine and designs the rules/logic to after this, feed the clients with recommendations, searches and geographical suggestion.
  - Client 2: Retail company. Internal Tool to improve the product creation chain, from buying the materials to designing the item. Java, React, Cypress, Karate. BFFs and Microservices.

#### Aug 2019-Jan 2022

## Java Developer, Ziath, Cambridge, UK

- Java (Spring Boot and Hibernate), Typescript (Angular), Maven, Git. Frameworks like electron, thymeleaf or Ionic. Jenkins and TeamCity. Some of the tasks required Linux to be used while developing.
  - -The company focused on manufacturing equipment for laboratories from the inception of the idea to the end of the product.

Mar-Jun 2018
Intern, Calidad Pascual, Madrid, Spain
Mar-Jul 2018
Fab-Lab, University San Pablo CEU, Madrid, Spain
Sep 2016-May 2017
Student Researcher, CNIC, Madrid, Spain

## **Education**

Dec 2020-Oct 2021

1:2 Master Stock Market and Financial Derivatives, UNED

Just for fun

Sep 2018-Sep 2019

1:1 MSc Computer Science, University of Greenwich, London

Sep 2013-Jul 2018

BSc Bilingual Biomedical Engineering, University of San Pablo CEU, Madrid, Spain

## **Additional Experience**

Sep 2018-June 2019

Bar Staff, Lower Deck, University of Greenwich, London

The main purpose of this activity was improving my English level and gaining confidence in a new environment at the same time I was monetizing my time.

## **Additional skills**

Spanish: NativeEnglish: AdvancedDriving licence

References available on request